hey there i just got this worksite tools
and equipment
20 volt automatic tire inflator in and
i'd like to give you a review on it it's
it's new it's from worksite
i had a 10-year unit that the battery
was dead on it and
i've been looking to upgrade i found
this on amazon and
i just want to give it a try and and
give you all an honest review and
and just see how it goes so uh let's
let's uh open it up and
see what we find out all right so go
ahead and get this opened up
cool it's got a nice bag to it looks
like it's got these zippers cool
i like it okay so far
yeah so just standard 20 volt lithium
battery
this is nice and portable check that out
so yeah so it's pretty lightweight i'm
guessing only a couple pounds
so you do get some adapters for gearing
up a basketball
different types of tips again i'm going
to read the directions kind of see
everything here
but yeah a little warranty card so you
can register that warranty
there's something else i want to point
out i thought was pretty neat that
there's some clips here on the sides and
back to hold the cord
inflator cord and these little clips on
the bottom
you can put your needles for the ball
inflator just right there so you have
easy access to them
all right my battery's all charged up
i'm going to go ahead and plug it into
the unit here
and show you a couple things
so to turn on the unit you hit the on
button and if you hit that again you can
cycle through the different units that
you can use to air up your
tire and that's pretty pretty neat and
then uh
if you want to adjust what psi you'd
like to air up your tire to
i just hit plus or minus
and when you plug it up to your tire the
valve
hit the on switch it'll air it up to
that psi
and then also something to keep in mind
that this display will go off after 60
seconds of
of not in use there's no off button that
i've seen here
plug this in
all right so again you turn it on like
so
i'm going to go ahead and air it up to
33 pistol i think was at 31 when i first
plugged it in it showed that
and i'm just going to turn this on it's
going to get a little loud so
here we go
yeah so it's showing the psi 32
35 32.5
wow okay that's awesome i figured i'd
check out my rv tire um actually plug
this in just a bit just to see where my
psi was and it says it was at 62 and
i need this to be at 65 so i'm gonna go
ahead and show you again
how easy this is you just plug it up to
the
valve and then um
it's going to give you the readout on
here
of what it currently is so it's 62.5 i'm
gonna go ahead and
hold it down all right so
i'm gonna go ahead and hit it on and
64.5
that's impressive so i'm going to just
show you this light here
it's kind of neat it's nice to have when
it's going to be dark out
all right so i'm kind of getting carried
away this thing's pretty slick it's so
quick to air up tires and
and plug in and see where my psi
currently is
so i'd like to i'd like to get these
tires to 33 psi right now they're 32.5
this won't take too long
here we go
just like that i was really impressed
with this tire inflator it
made quick work of the pop-up and the
two vehicles i have here
i didn't have to fill them up too much
but it was still very quick my old
inflator
uh just to do what i did there would
take two or three minutes of just
sitting there waiting
but uh yeah i really like the adjustment
here to be able to dial in your psi
and and there's no guess work you're not
popping
the the tire gauge on to see then
popping your
inflator on and then guessing and
putting the gauge back on to see where
you're at
this takes the guesswork right out of it
you dial in your psi
and you're good to go so that's that's a
winner for me highly recommend the
worksite
tiring automatic tire inflator and it's
on amazon right
now excellent five stars for sure